One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
The Mysterious Sea and
The Skeleton Brook!
Luffy and Crew's
New Pirate Ship
Thousand Sunny
This is paradise, paradise.
Taking a nice bath while being rocked by the waves...
This is the best.
This is my room.
Medical Room
Got it!
We caught a cool shark!
Put it in! Put it in!
Put it in the fish tank!
Put it in!
Get in there!
Another one came in.
A shark.
Well, isn't this room perfect?
The room is fine, but a shark?! Those idiots.
Alright, let's go see it!
Let's see the tank!
Hey! Did the shark get in?
It's the one with the big horns!
Yes, it did, but...
All the fish you caught so far are gone.
That was obviously going to happen when you think about the consequences!
The ship continues its
favorable voyage.
Damn it!
Turn this bastard into dinner!
Sanji! Make BBQ out of this stupid shark!
Wait up, you novice!
This is a fresh fish.
Maybe some sushi... boiling it adding some spicy vinegar miso...
Tempura could also be good.
I'm getting hungry!
That was a nice bath.
Hey! Something's floating in the sea.
What is it?
A barrel?
It has "treasure" written on it.
Tribute to the Sea-God
You're right!
Could it be...
Some lost stuff from a treasure ship?!
Treasure?!
Treasure, treasure, we've discovered a treasure!
It's a shame.
It seems to be liquor and food supplies.
How can you tell without looking inside?!
It has " Tribute to the Sea-God" written on it, doesn't it?
That's a floating barrel someone sends when they pray to have a safe trip.
These offerings are sent to receive the sea's divine blessing.
In short, the word "tribute" means "to God".
What, so it was pointless picking it up?
After all it's booze, isn't it?
Let's drink it.
Idiot! You'll get punished!
You'll be fine as long as you pray, won't you?
I won't pray to some God.
It's said that liquor which is cared for by the sea waves has an exceptional taste.
That's something we must taste!
Alright! Let's have a toast!
After drinking it, we're supposed to refill the barrel with new offerings and set it adrift again.
Open it!
Hurry!
Hey, God! We'll be receiving this!
What God?!
Who was the one that beat the hell out of this "God" at the Sky Island...
Alright! It's open!
Something flew out!
What is that?!
A red light...?!
What?
What does this mean?
The liquor flew out, sparkled and then disappeared.
It was a flare.
A flare?
Could it be a curse from the Sea-God?
It might have been just a prank, but...
Probably...
Someone might be tracking this ship from now on.
N-No way...!
Some sort of trap?!
By opening the barrel, we've informed someone that we're here?!
We really can't see anyone one, but...
This atmospheric pressure...
The cloud currents are moving really fast.
I can't see anyone!
Nothing here either!
Everyone, to your posts!
Head south-southeast!
A great storm is approaching within five minutes!
I can't see it but,
If she says so, it must be very close!
Nami, which way?!
2 o'clock ahead!
It's no use!
We're facing a head wind!
We're being pushed back!
Hey!
Do you really think this is all this boat can handle?
That's right!
Everyone raise the sails!
We're bringing out the paddle!
That?!
I really like that! It's so cool!
Soldier Dock System!
Channel Zero!
Cola Engine!
Paddle Ship Sunny!
Go!
Come on!
We made it through...
We made it through, but...
What's with this sea?
It's not even night, and yet...
This eerie fog has made everything dark.
Perhaps...
We've ventured into that sea area...
We're not prepared yet!
We've already arrived at the Fishman Island?
No, first we need to get through the sea where ghosts come out.
That's right.
Don't let your guard down.
Without a doubt... this area is already... the famous...
Florian Triangle.
The outrageous sea where everything mysteriously disappears!
Eh?! G-Gho... G-Gho...
Ghosts come out, right in this sea.
Stop joking!
How come everyone besides me knows about that story?!
We heard it from Old Lady Kokoro.
There are living skeletons here.
L-Living skeletons?!
That's just your imagination.
Don't scare him over such absurd stuff.
Listen, Usopp.
Every year, more than 100 ships mysteriously vanish within this very sea.
Moreover, it is said that a ghost ship with the souls of deceased people wanders this sea.
I don't want that!
You should've said that earlier!
And what if I had?
I would be prepared!
Prepared some items to disperse the evil spirits!
Usopp, lend me some of them too!
What's this voice?!
It appeared!
The ghost ship!
What's with this song?
It's the song of evil spirits!
Don't listen to it!
Close your ears or you'll be cursed!
No matter what kind of thing the ghost says to you, don't listen to him!
If you answer back, he'll drag you to sea with him!
Evil spirits are always hunting travelers!
Who could be... riding this ship...?
If he's an enemy, I'll just chop his head off.
Something... is there.
Going to deliver...
Binks' Sake...
Why do I have to go?
I wanna go back.
That's why I told you I'd go by myself.
No way!
What if our ship gets cursed because of your stupidity?
I had terrible luck!
Nami-san, it's alright!
I'll protect you, Nami-san!
Nami, you wanted to find the treasure ship, didn't you?
There's no way this is a treasure ship!
You saw it, didn't you?!
That moving skeleton!
He must be the treasure's guardian.
Anyway, let's look for him!
Evil spirits, begone! Evil spirits, begone!
Luffy, rest in peace...!
Nice to meet you! Yohohoho!
Skeleton Gentleman
Brook
Forgive my discourtesy, I couldn't greet you when we first met.
You surprised me!
It's been many decades since the last time I met a person.
Ship after ship, it's the same, just ghost ships wandering around here.
It's kind of scary!
Well, make yourselves at home and come inside.
We'll be able to talk more relaxed.
Look, it's talking!
The afro-skeleton is talking!
Unbelievable!
My, my!
What a lovely young lady!
Beautiful indeed!
Eh... no... not at all...
I have a good eye for beautiful ladies!
Although, skeletons don't have eyes!
Can you please show me your panties?
As if!
My, my, quite a harsh one!
The flesh came right off of my bones...
Although I'm only a skeleton.
Shut up!
Hey, can you poop?
There are plenty of other questions to ask besides that!
Yes, I can.
There's no need to answer!
Nevermind that!
Firstly! Although you're nothing but bones, how can you be alive and talk?!
What exactly are you?
Why are you here?
What's happening on this ship?!
And what's happening on this sea?!
Answer all of this now!
Nevermind all that.
Hey you!
Join my crew!
Sure, why not.
How do you do?
I'm afraid that while traveling, my ship ran into quite a bit of trouble!
I am "Just Dead Bones" Brook!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
What the hell?!
Who is this guy?!
Oh my, oh my!
How harsh!
It's a skeleton!
Oh, what a beautiful woman!
Would you allow me to see your panties?
Stop it, you perverted skeleton!
Damn it! Skeletons can't talk, or walk, or have afros!
This is a dream!
It's gotta be a dream!
Really?!
What a relief... just a dream...
Hey, Luffy!
What's with this guy?
Isn't he funny?
He's part of our crew now.
I don't care, I won't let him be!
Why the hell did you guys go with him?
Wasn't it to stop him from doing something like this?!
Sorry...
It's nothing to get so worked up about.
Let's go inside now.
We can have dinner!
Who are you to decide that?!
Oh, what a wonderful dining room!
And the kitchen!
This is such a marvelous ship!
Yeah, that's 'cuz this super guy made it!
You've really got an eye for quality.
Hey, don't get attached to him, Franky.
But what I'm truly looking forward to is the food.
I haven't had any good food for so many years...
I've lived so long with these hunger pains that I feared I was just skin and bones...
Although I'm a skeleton and don't have any skin at all!
Skull joke!
As a gentleman, I enjoy the time spent awaiting my meal...
Dinner, yeah!
Food! Food!
Chef, please bring me some milk to drink!
Just shut up and wait!
So anyway, Korobokle...
Oh no, it's Brook.
Oh, I'm sorry, but I'm afraid I don't yet have your name...?
Me?
I'm Luffy.
So, anyway, what are you?
You two didn't even ask that kind of thing?!
We can get rid of the skeleton later.
Right now, it's time to eat!
An entire octopus meal.
It looks good!
Hey, Brook, make sure you eat a lot!
Sanji's food is the best!
Oh, but...
I'm afraid that my heart is even emptier than my stomach...
My fair lady, your portion seems to be a little large.
Would you care to trade?
There's a lot more left, so just eat your own!
The Revival Fruit?
So you ate a devil fruit....
That's correct.
To tell you the truth, I died once years ago.
First, clean your face off.
How'd you get yourself so dirty?
The Revival Fruit...
Grants the ability to resurrect, so as a "resurrection human"…
You have the promise of a second life.
It's quite a mysterious ability.
Yes, at that time, I was a pirate just like you.
Excuse me.
I just wanna beat some manners into you...
Long ago...
On the ship I was on before,
The crew I was a part of came to this sea of devils.
However...
Unluckily for us, incredibly powerful foes appeared.
Our whole crew was killed in battle.
I, of course, died as well.
When I was alive, the Revival Fruit simply made me unable to swim...
However, that day the fruit became more than just that!
My soul...
Has returned from the underworld to this world!
If I was able to find my body quickly, I would have been revived.
However, as you can see, the fog makes this sea difficult to navigate.
I became lost!
I searched for my body as a lost soul for an entire year.
And finally, I found it!
However, my body had been reduced to nothing but bones!
When I saw it, my eyes widened very much in surprise...
Although I have no eyes!
You're so stupid!
You got lost just like Zoro!
Hey.
So that's when you became a talking skeleton?
I didn't know a devil fruit could even bring someone back to life...
But even after you come back to life, you're still unable to swim,
so now you're just cursed.
But normally hair can't grow on bones...
I've never seen a skeleton with an afro before.
Oh, I just had strong roots.
Whatever you say...
So, that means you aren't a ghost?
You're human?
Even though you're not really...
Yes, I dislike ghosts myself!
If I see one, I cry out in fear!
Have you ever looked in a mirror?
No, not a mirror!
H-Hey, w-wait a s-sec!
Y-You...
Why don't you...
Why don't you have a reflection in the mirror?!
A vampire?!
Really?!
Awesome!
N-Now that you mention it,
You don't have a shadow either!
He's right!
What are you really?!
Why are you so calm?
W-We're all really scared here! Because of you!
I'll tell you this.
I've been traveling this sea for so many years...
However, me being a skeleton and having no shadow are two unrelated matters.
To be continued.
No, tell us now!
My shadow was stolen from me years ago.
Stolen?
Your shadow?
After seeing you here living and talking, I'm not really surprised by anything you say...
But can that really happen?
Yes, it can.
Having my shadow stolen from me means that I am no longer able to exist in the world's light.
If I were to be hit with the light of the sun...
My body would...
My body would disintegrate!
I once saw...
Someone with this same curse disappear when bathed in sunlight...
It was enough to make my hair stand on end!
Although I'm a skeleton.
A shadow is reflected on the ground by sunlight.
Therefore, I myself cannot be reflected in something like a mirror or photograph.
And here I exist, unable to be in light, with all my crewmates long dead!
Your life's been pretty miserable.
But I lived through it all!
Even though I'm just bones.
I'm "Just Dead Bones" Brook!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
Why're you so happy?
Hey hey, what's wrong?
You okay?
Today is such a marvelous day!
I've seen people once more!
For so many years I've sailed through this ocean,
The fog making it so dark I couldn't even tell when the days passed...
All my crewmates were dead...
I was all alone on a ship that couldn't steer...
Sailing aimlessly for many, many years...
I was so lonely!
So very lonely,
And so very scared...
I just wanted to die...
But I lived on...
People are my happiness!
All of you are my joy!
I'm so happy that I would cry if I were able!
You asked me to join your crew, correct?
That made me very happy, thank you very much.
However, I must refuse your offer.
Why?!
As I told you before, my shadow was stolen, and I am unable to return to the light of the world.
Right now I'm being protected by the fog of this devils' sea.
However,
If I were to leave this ocean with you, it would only be a matter of time before my body disappeared.
I'll stay here, waiting for the joyous day when I can regain my shadow!
What are you going on about?!
If you need your shadow, I'll get it back for you.
You said someone stole it, right?
Who was it?
Where is he?
You are a very kind person.
I'm surprised...
However, I won't tell you.
I can't tell you, who I've just met, to go and die for me.
Is the enemy really that strong?
That's fine, but can't you at least tell us his name?
No, I cannot.
You may find him if I do!
I don't know if I will find him before my second life is over.
If I do find him, I've decided I will fight him, but...
That aside...
Let's sing a song.
Music is my pride!
I was the musician on my crew.
Really?!
You're a musician?!
Then you've really gotta join our crew, idiot!
Let's sing a fun song together!
Hey, what is it?
What's wrong?
G-G-G...
Ghost!
There's something there!
I'm scared, there's a ghost!
Cool!
I'm getting out of here!
Why're we shaking?
No... it can't be...!
What a thing to happen...!
Those guys're watching this ship?!
Please look!
This ship is being blocked!
This is what caused that shaking!
This is the back of the gate...
Gate?
Which means...!
Look at the back of the ship!
What is it?
Did you, perhaps, pick up a floating barrel...?
We did!
That was a trap!
This ship has been targeted since then.
What do you mean?
We've been right here the whole time...
Why is there an island there?
That is the wandering ghost island...
Thriller Bark.
Hold on...
The log pose isn't reacting at all!
That's correct.
It is because this island traveled here from the distant West Blue.
Oh, but today is such a lucky day.
Not only did I see people once more, but my deepest wish has come true as well!
He's so light...!
Of course!
Since I'm "just dead bones", I have to be light!
Now please, find a way to go through that gate behind you and leave this place.
Do not drop anchor here.
I was so happy to meet you.
I will never forget your delicious food!
Farewell!
If fate will have it, let us meet again!
Hey, wait, Brook!
Didn't he eat a devil fruit?!
What are you doing?!
He's running on the water!
Woah, cool!
A-Anyway, Luffy...
Let's do what he said!
We don't know what's going on here, but we do know that it's dangerous!
Did you say something?
He's going!
Translation & initial timing, Vegapunk Fansubs
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, Halee
Raw provider, SOFCJ-Raws